Rise and shine, sir. Mr.
Kakyoin, are you feeling any better today?
To be perfectly honest, this new way
of life isn't exactly agreeing with me.
I'm feeling a little on edge.
And have you had any discomfort?
No, I haven't actually.
The painkillers must be working.
Good.
Excellent news.
We're thrilled that you're feeling better.
So, Doctor, about these, how
long will I have to keep them on?
The thing is, I can't
afford to wait any longer.
Look, Kakyoin, while
your eyes will recover,
your condition is nothing
to be taken lightly.
You'll be in our care for quite
some time, so please be patient.
The fact of the matter is, we just don't
know how long you're going to remain here.
Just kidding.
It's true your body still needs
time to properly heal itself.
But for some strange reason,
doctors from the Speedwagon Foundation
recently contacted us out of the blue.
And they've asked that we entrust
your medical care to them.
Though I have little doubt
their state-of-the-art
medical treatments will prove
to be more than effective.
But tell me, who are you
behind that schoolboy facade?
Surely you must know, that
foundation is world famous.
I can't imagine they'd want anything to
do with an average high school student.
Let's just say I'm fortunate to
have a very dependable friend.
Thank you for everything, Mr.
Joestar.
I suppose we'll be seeing each
other again sooner than we thought.
Jotaro, Polnareff, Avdol, Iggy.
Just hang in there.
Let me cry.
The joy ofgemony.
You can turn it to me!
My eyes again.
The fate of the
tomb of a dream?
That is the one who has been taken.
The devil's soul.
The devil's love.
Hora
Hear!
Located in southern Egypt
is the city of Luxor.
To the ancient Egyptians, however,
it was the site of Thebes.
And it is in this location,
on the west bank of the Nile,
that the pharaohs of
old were laid to rest.
It is known as the Valley of the Kings.
Have you heard of the tomb of
the great king Tutankhamen?
It lies here in the Valley of the Kings.
Wow, this place is chock full of history.
If what I've heard is true, some
of the residents of this area?
Still dig beneath their
houses in search of treasure.
without permission from the government.
Think those ancient guys left
behind any undiscovered treasure?
Perhaps they did.
You guys see where the
old man ran off to oh
Yes to the bathroom, and he took
Iggy since he can detect enemies.
Is that so do you need to go? Hmm?
My might if it's a normal bathroom?
Oh
Oh, my God!
The climate in this place is so damn arid,
the crab dries up, turns
to dust, and blows away.
Which means instead of using water,
this toilet relies solely on wind.
And I don't see any toilet paper.
Hmm, is that?
Exactly as I thought.
Some sort of sand basin.
So you wipe your ass with sand?
Desert sand is as sterile as it gets.
Oh, my God!
I think I'll pull a polnareff and
wait till we get back to the hotel.
What's the point of a shack
if you're going in a hole?
You might as well just do
your business behind a rock.
This thing is weird even
for a place like Egypt.
Hmm, this doesn't make the
slightest bit of sense.
Who in their right mind would think
to put an electrical outlet in a rock?
I wonder what it's used for.
There's no electricity out here.
The damn thing electrocuted me! Mr.
Joestar, is everything all right?
We should probably get a move on. Huh?
Oh, right.
Just give me a second.
That scared the living
daylights out of me.
I can't believe it's still live.
I guess the cables must run
underground or something.
You can never tell with this place.
It's like traveling
through a fantasy land.
Card of the Goddess Best.
Stand user, Mariah.
Now how did that old saying go again?
Curiosity killed the cat.
We could make it to Cairo in two days,
but since all of us are
injured and exhausted,
why don't we spend tonight and tomorrow
in Luxor and use that time to recuperate?
Hmm. Hmm.
Sounds good to me.
Ever since we got to Egypt,
the enemy stands have been
getting stronger and stronger.
We've been winning these battles
by the skin of our teeth.
Hmm.
Hey, Mr.
Joestar, is something wrong?
I'm fine.
My prosthetic hand is acting funny.
That's all.
It's nothing to worry about.
I probably just need to oil the joints.
Hey there, shopkeeper.
Can you please do
something about that radio?
It's busted.
Man, that's peculiar.
It was made in Japan, and I
just bought the darn thing.
Gah!
Well, it's just static now.
Turn it off!
Huh?
Mr. Joestar?
Hmm?
Yeah, you're right.
We'd probably be in our best interest
to rest up before heading to Cairo.
Remember, we can't let our guard down.
Okay, let's find a hotel.
What's going on?
Thanks for the drinks, mister.
Come again?
Hey, look at that.
The radio's working again.
What the?
Why is the hammer suddenly
so heavy? I can't...
What the hell?
Ah!
Hm?
The nails!
Oh, God, it hurts!
Hey, old man, did you bang
your finger with the hammer?
You gotta be more careful.
You can't just go throwing
hammers around, it's dangerous!
Jeez.
Mr.
Joestar, it's time to wake up.
Mr. Joestar!
Hey, hurry it up in there!
Polnareff is going on
and on about the four
of us finding somewhere to eat breakfast.
Hurry and wake him up, Avdol!
He's got five minutes
before I come up there!
You know, I thought old people
were supposed to get up early!
Damn, smart Alec.
He has no respect for his elders.
Tell him I'll be down in just a minute.
Right.
Well, that's bizarre.
Why did my watch stop working?
You know Mr. Joestar.
Hmm?
You toss and turn in your sleep
quite a bit for a man your age.
You haven't noticed yet, but
you're facing the wrong way.
You went to bed facing south, but
woke up northward like a compass.
Glad you still have a youthful spirit.
I'll be downstairs when you're ready.
Hmm...
Hmm, something strange has been going
on ever since yesterday afternoon,
and for some reason my
hand is still acting up.
What is up with this freaky chair?
The blasted thing's moving on its own!
If I didn't know any better, I'd guess
the floors in this place were slanted!
For such a ritzy hotel, it sure
does seem like it was cheaply made.
So, where should we go today?
Well, I had an amazing time looking around
Karnak, so I'd say something like that.
How about the Valley
of the Queens instead?
What the hell do you think you're
doing, you old pervert jackass?
I don't understand.
What the hell just happened?
I do appreciate your forwardness, but
you need to work on your approach,
you naughty, naughty man.
But that said, you're just my Deep. Mwah!
Oh my god!
I was right.
Something's wrong here.
Really wrong.
And it's been this way ever
since yesterday afternoon.
Wait, what the?
They're stuck to my hand. Hang on.
It's all starting to make sense.
The reason why all these metal
objects are suddenly attracted to me.
But it can't be.
That's impossible.
It looks like I was right.
My body's turned into a magnet!
I think this insanity might
be the work of a stand.
But if that's the case,
why can't I see it?
How could these knives and forks
fly at me if the stand isn't nearby?
There's no way!
Could this really be a
side-effect of the shock
I took from the socket
on that rock yesterday?
I can't get out of it!
Oh no, it didn't even cross my mind
that the escalator's made of steel!
This doesn't look good!
The magnetic pull's getting
stronger by the minute!
You there, lady in the micro
miniskirt, I need you to help me out.
Please, miss, I'm begging you.
Not to be rude, but your
chain's wrapped around my body,
and it'd be nice if you'd get it off
me before I'm shredded to pieces.
There's not much time,
so if you could push the emergency
stop button, that'd be swell.
Come on, lady, the chains
are pulling me tighter.
This thing's going to rip
off my hands and feet!
What's the problem?
Are you even listening?
Enjoy the ride, Joseph Joestar.
What the hell?
You can't be serious!
If you know who I am,
that would make you the stand user!
So it's you? Damn it!
All you were the stand user all along!
Once you've made contact with the
magnetic field surrounding my stand bast!
You've sealed your fate
as there's no escape?
from its deadly power.
Please, let me out!
Someone stop this infernal escalator!
Hey, that's it!
I'll push the emergency stop
button, using my Hermit Purple!
That doesn't make sense! Where is it?
The only reason that I'd
have this much trouble
finding it would be if it didn't have one?
But that can't be possible!
What escalator doesn't
have a shut-off button?
It's pulling me in!
My neck! My neck!
It's gonna cut off my head!
I'm done for!
Save me!
Mr.
Joestar, pay attention!
I'm gonna die!
Hello, Mr. Joestar!
Why, decalmitation!
Goodbye, crew!
The escalator stopped some time ago.
I already pushed the
emergency stop button.
It's on the side instead of in the front.
Everything is Aqua!
I just inspected this escalator
and it's in working order!
You'll be happy to know the
emergency button works fine.
Hello, sir.
You must be the owner
of this establishment.
If you don't mind, I'll be
needing your signature right here.
Hmm?
I'm lost, Mr. Joestar. What happened?
A stand.
An enemy stand managed
to tag me yesterday.
Now my body's turned into one big magnet.
you see the user turned me
into a magnet and now metal
is attracted to me would
you pull this thing off of
me it looks like the magnetic
pull is becoming stronger
the longer the stand's
power remains in effect huh
that's her that woman there
is the stand user we've
got to find a way to stop
her and i have to get rid of
this insane magnetic pull
somehow i won't be able to
move my body at We should also
get Jojirou and Polnareff.
What?
It's so heavy! Not again!
Avdol, there's no time to get the others!
Just look, she's getting away!
Move away, Mr. Joestar!
Just run after her!
Right, on it!
I have to get a good look at her face!
But this is...
Clever.
She went into the ladies' room.
Now what?
Guess I'm going in.
My life is on the line here.
So I guess I have to catch
this vixen no matter what!
What's the hold up?
That's what I'd like to know.
Avdol went inside to find him,
but he hasn't come back either.
Oh no!
What if those two snuck off? What?
They're probably having an
amazing breakfast as we speak!
It's more likely he's taking
his time in the bathroom.
But if they don't show up in the next
five minutes, we'll go look for him.
Yeah, the bathroom.
Guess that makes sense.
You know, come to think of it, the
bathrooms in this hotel are spotless.
So, Mr.
Joestar, now that we're in here...
Hmm.
It's just as I expected.
We have a problem on our hands.
Shh!
Forgive me, but I...
I haven't the foggiest
clue which stall she's in.
Do you have a way to find her?
Well, for one, she's got amazing legs.
Legs? That's right.
Just look for those legs.
Believe me when I say you can't miss them.
So, we have to take a peek.
No, she's not in this one.
Nope.
No again.
Mr.
Joestar, I think I've found her.
Come over here.
Are these her legs?
Oh my, you're that handsome
fellow from before.
You came all the way here to find me.
You dirty boy, the heart wants
what the heart wants. Mwah!
Holy shit!
It's, it's the hag from earlier!
From the second floor!
This is bad.
We got the wrong person,
but I thought for sure those
were the legs of the stand user.
How could you screw that up?
Run, Eldo!
Help!
I don't deserve to be
treated like a peeping Tom!
Hold her as the one who should be
getting called a dirty pervert!
Dirty old man!
Disgusting!
Perverts!
Oh no, he's feroomgious.
Look, there she is!
She's headed that way!
Damn it!
How did that harlot get
so far away? After her!
I forgot to tell you, whatever you do,
it's imperative that you refrain
from touching any electrical outlets.
It doesn't matter where they are.
Stay away from them!
She manifests her stand
through the outlets.
The moment you touch one,
you'll get zapped and the magnetism
will begin to take effect.
I'm afraid I already did, Mr.
Joestar.
What?
Where did it happen?
I touched one when I pushed the
emergency stop button on the escalator.
There was a socket directly beside it.
If only I had known.
Damn, that conniving minx.
Excuse me, Mr. Joestar.
Would you mind giving me some space?
I can't run with you
stuck to me like this.
I was about to say the same to you, Efdo.
What are you talking about, sir?
You're the one who's running close to me.
If what I know about magnets is
true, we're being forced together!
I cannot believe she managed to
turn me into a magnet as well. Mr.
Joestar, I really hate saying this, but...
Yeah, I know, we've gotten
ourselves into a world of trouble!
This is ridiculous!
I'm at a complete loss!
She's so powerful!
Thank you.
Now my body's a magnet.
The magnetic pull is
stronger than it was before.
That woman is pure evil.
So what should we do if we don't get free?
I've run away from fights before,
but I've only done so when running
was part of the overall strategy.
The real showdown begins now.